...all the weekends of a given month
plus three weeknights."
- That's absurd.
- No.
You initialed it. See? "L.H., L.H., L.H."
Okay, wait. I only initialed it
because I never thought it would happen.
(Leonard:)I initialed another clause naming you
my sidekick in case I get superpowers.
Hm. Yes, you did.
(Sheldon:)Now to review, the following provisions
are hereby activated.
In the refrigerator, as opposed to two
separate shelves and one communal shelf...
(Sheldon:)...the three of us now get individual shelves
and the door becomes communal.
(Sheldon:)Next, apartment vacuuming shall be
increased from two to three times a week...
(Sheldon:)...to accommodate the increased
accumulation of dead skin cells.
(Sheldon:)The bathroom schedule.
I'm given to understand...
(Sheldon:)...women have different needs,
so we'll have to discuss that.
(Steph:)- I'm going to bed.
- But, yeah, but...
(Sheldon:)At least take this with you.
(Sheldon:)Look, and have Stephanie
initial here, here, here, here...
(Sheldon:)...and here.
(Sheldon:)This states that she does not now...
(Sheldon:)...nor does she intend to play a percussive
or brass instrument.
[SIGHS]
[HUMMING]
[IN HIGH-PITCHED VOICE]
Sure sounds like a tumor...
(Sheldon:)...pressing on the auditory nerve.